# Yode Wang

# **UX** Designer

yode0419@gmail.com.tw



+886 911 027827



https://yode0419.github.io/portfolio



#### **Profile**

I am an entry-level designer, a challenger in the field of UX design, with a background in civil structural engineering. Despite the different fields, I possess core capabilities required in this area: communication, coordination, design thinking, and problem-solving. Drawing, 3D modeling, presenting ideas, and considering feasibility are my specialties.

During my journey of self-study for this career transition, I have completed the Google UX Design course, accumulated UX portfolio projects, and built up my personal website. I am excited to bring my passion to UX and product design, aiming to provide users with enhanced experiences.

### **Experiences**

2023.06 - 2023.08

#### Google UX Design Professional Certificate

Learning UX / Portfolio / Web Development

2016.09 - 2023.06

#### **Structural Engineer**

**TYLIN Construction Consultant** Structural Design / Bridge Design / Project Management

- · Taoyuan Metro Green Line
- · Kaohsiung Metro Red Line
- · Taoyuan Airport Terminal 3
- · Hualien-Taitung Railway Dual-Track Project

2019.13 - 2020.12

## Working Holiday in Australia

Perth / Melbourne

- · Crazy Sales Warehouse
- · The Pamphleteers Mail Delivery
- · Treviso Farm Grape Worker

#### Education

2013.09 - 2015.09

## **National Taiwan University**

Master's Degree in Civil Engineering, Structural Division

2009.09 - 2013.09

# **National Taiwan University**

Bachelor's Degree in Civil Engineering

#### Skills

C	raphic Desigr
F	gma
Р	hotoshop
П	ustrator
Р	rocreate

3D Modeling
Blender SketchUp
Engineering Drawing

**AutoCAD** 

Front-End Development
HTML
CSS
JavaScript
Bootstrap

Office
Word
PowerPoin
Excel
VBA

## Languages English (Intermediate Level) French (Beginner Level)